[{"answer": "I'm running out of time.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 15, "question": "It's a complete scam so you've got to stop this, okay?", "qSentId": 14}, {"answer": "It's typical Brokaw, I mean, I think there's so many of us -- I'll put myself on the first of the list, people who are grateful to Tom.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "What do you make of the way that he had responded to this?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Oh God, he is the best.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "And Deborah, for people who don't know Tom as well as you do, what kind of man is he?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "I was always surprised that liberals are being surprised.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "What did you make of it?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "Oh absolutely.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "Is it a clever tactic?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "Could it not backfire for Rand Paul?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "And tell me this.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "What are we talking about here tonight?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "I don't think that's true.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "How do the right deal with the inarguable fact that abortion levels are falling in America and the primary reason for this is increased awareness in use of contraception?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "I'm going to explain why this is not true now.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "How do you on the right handle that situation?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "There is proof.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "Do you think it's good that more American women are using contraceptive?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "There is proof that with the greater availability of contraception and the greater availability of abortion, there will be more illegitimacy.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Do you think it's good?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "I don't really care.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "Are you against then more American women using contraceptions in a responsible manner?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "I mean, I don't know.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "You don't care?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Because I'm fascinated with the debt ceiling.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "From the single biggest health issues women in the world, why wouldn't you care?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "I'm opposed to promise you (ph) (inaudible) but you don't clarify that, so...", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "Well now, I'm putting you on the spot, are you in favor of it or not?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "It's not that responsible.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "Isn't a good thing for America that more women are using contraception in a responsible way?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "Any fall is a good thing.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "I don't think what?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "In the number of abortions.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "Fall?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "Because I like this girl and your mother is a catholic.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "Why did you have us?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "Oh, I figured out if we kept on scrum (ph), we'd end up with a couple of you.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "So, you and mom never actually talked about whether you want kids or not?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "Well, the biggest when I've had in this whole process is that Alexander Payne invited me to come on down...", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "How do you feel, I mean, what a moment for you after 80 movies to finally get nominee for a lead role?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "Well, he is a prince as far as I'm concerned.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "What was your reaction when you heard about this?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "Well, the best I ever saw had done, and you know, he wasn't really a newscaster when I was young, was (inaudible)", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "He has that stoppable (ph) authority which is good in a ray (ph) I think isn't it?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "No surprise to you that Tom Brokaw has carried a on working despite having been diagnosed.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "I'm sorry?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "He's just, you know, every now and then you're around across (inaudible) one.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "That's why (ph)?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "Did you know her at all?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "And you to a daughter that became actor as well?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "The first play I was ever in was directed Mr. (inaudible) and it was called The Shadow of a Gunman it was on Sean O'Casey on Broadway and the first time the act of studio ever did a play on Broadway.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "You also, I think in your early acting career you've got that (inaudible) and sometimes you weren't even allowed out to do a final curtain call for the audience because anyone who kill (inaudible) the mystery of you still dead on stage, right?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "Fabulous.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "When, you know, you didn't get the curtain call then and now you're going to win an Oscar, I mean a good moment, right?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "He said to me about four inches in the wild (inaudible) one on one and about eight in the morning.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "Is it true, John Wayne said to you, they're going to hate you for this?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "and I said -- maybe and we got in Berkley I'm a GD (ph) hero.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "And did they?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "Even in England when we went there and Gatsby was shot a lot of it I mean the Gatsby we were in and we shot a lot time with it and I run everyday.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "Even now?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "I've never had a cigarette, never had a cup of coffee, never had a drink, however, I did miss a decade to Vicodin.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "This is fame list and yet you have never had an alcohol drink or even a coffee in your life, is that true?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "The TV show with a doctor who was addicted to Vicodin?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "Huge Laurie?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "The immediacy of his response time and I have always thought one thing that I insist on and if the actors won't do it, you just find a way to get them to do it by the way you talk to them and deal with them in the scene immediately.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "Why from your perspective?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "But weren't they a fourth division team?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Since she was nine years old.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "The craft of making movies, the technique?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "I'm there.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "I'll watch the World Cup with you, how about that?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "You mean, I was sitting next to Bubba Watson?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "Well, now I feel great, you know, I got to met him so but, you know, when hearing the story and listen to you all talk back there, I mean you learn a lot about a person and you could see that he was a big sports fan.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "So how do you feel now you know you were next to this legend?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "Pretty, pretty good I think the first couple of segments were very good.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 636, "question": "How many laughs are you getting out of all this?", "qSentId": 635}, {"answer": "It's wild, you know.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "How has being the master's champion changed your life?", "qSentId": 640}, {"answer": "It changed everything, you know, when you step on the golf course now people expect you to play good.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 643, "question": "Does it change everything?", "qSentId": 642}, {"answer": "Yeah, everybody expects you to play good so that's means ...", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "Any down sides to the fame that's come with it for you?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "Well, I feel like I have a chance if everybody else is getting wasted like that.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "And so close to the Super Bowl Sunday at the Phoenix Waste Management Open, one of the great titles in world sport and how do you feel when you (inaudible) when someone called the waste management open?", "qSentId": 661}, {"answer": "I've slightly worried he's got a more natural rhythm to his swing, yeah.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 678, "question": "Is that swing better than yours or is that?", "qSentId": 677}, {"answer": "Yeah for, you know, just watching me on TV and stuff and I've never said anything to him he just grabs the club and swings.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "He looks like he can hold of a club there?", "qSentId": 679}, {"answer": "I loved playing golf because it's always different it always something new and I just won my club championship last week in Scottsville so, you know, I still playing in the club tournaments at home.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 684, "question": "Do you ever wish you've done anything else in life or you just still love getting up and playing golf all day?", "qSentId": 683}, {"answer": "I've watched a few things but it's so political.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 698, "question": "Are you into the Sochi stuff at the moment?", "qSentId": 697}, {"answer": "You know, it's sad that somebody has to feel they have to come out, like just be who you are.", "docId": "140211pmt", "aSentId": 704, "question": "What do you think of that?", "qSentId": 703}]